README.md 3/3/2021

Marco Lackovic



Resume

- Last update 03-Mar-2021
- Download the latest version in PDF

Bio

Software engineer with 6 years of software development experience in the industry, 7 years in the academia as research fellow and teaching assistant. EESTEC alumni. Born and raised in Italy, relocated to Estonia in 2015.

Languages

• Italian: native speaker

English: fluent

• Estonian: intermediate (B1)

· Croatian: elementary

Work Experience

Full stack developer

• Concise, 2020 → present

Domain: Parking platform

User base: millions - world

- Tech stack: java, javascript, spring-boot, spring-data-jdbc, spring-mvc, spring-webflux, hibernate, lombok, junit, spock, gwen, groovy, gradle, maven, flyway, node.js, npm, mocha, docker, postgresql, git, markdown
- Tools: windows, wsl-2, archlinux, ubuntu, intellij-idea, visual-studio-code, teamcity, slack, jira, bitbucket
- GrabCAD, 2019 → 2020, 7 months

README.md 3/3/2021

- Domain: 3D modeling community management
- User base: millions world
- Tech stack: ruby, javascript, rails, rspec, sidekiq, redis, vuejs2, angularjs, elasticsearch, rest, postgresql-10, git, docker, markdown
- Tools: windows, wsl, rubymine, visual-studio-code, tortoisegit, jenkins, slack, jira, github
- GrabCAD, 2018 → 2019, 1 year
 - Domain: 3D printing order management
 - User base: hundreds world
 - Tech stack: typescript, graphql, node.js, npm, reactjs, semantic-ui, jest, enzyme, apollo, typeorm, postgresql-10, express, git, docker, kubernetes, markdown
 - o Tools: windows, visual-studio-code, tortoisegit, teamcity, slack, jira, github
- Helmes, 2016 → 2018, 2 years and 10 months
 - Domain: Mobile phone repair management
 - User base: thousands Northern Europe
 - Tech stack: C#, javascript, asp.net-mvc, angularjs, yarn, bootstrap, rest, iis-express, sql-server, git
 - Tools: windows, visual-studio-2015, visual-studio-2017, rider, octopus, postman, slack, jira, confluence, ssms, tortoisegit, bitbucket
- Helmes, 2015, 10 months
 - o Domain: Healthcare
 - User base: hundreds Estonia
 - Tech stack: C#, javascript, webforms, soap, bootstrap, telerik, sql-server
 - Tools: windows, visual-studio-2008, visual-studio-2012, ssms

Research fellow

- UNICAL, 2011 → 2015, 4 years: Distributed Data Mining, Grid Computing
 - Tech stack: java, globus-toolkit, soap, web-services, latex
 - Tools: linux, eclipse

Teaching assistant

• UNICAL, 2007 → 2015, 8 years: Object Oriented Programming, Multi-Threading Programming

README.md 3/3/2021

- Tech stack: java, c++
- Tools: linux, eclipse, libreoffice

Education

- UNICAL 2011: PhD in Computer Engineering
- UNICAL 2007: Master in Computer Engineering

Links

- Stackoverflow
- LinkedIn
- Google Scholar

GitHub

- Profile
- Contributions